## KAREL VERSCHRAEGEN

**FULL STACK DEVELOPER** 



karelverschraegen.com



github.com/KarelVerschraegen/



karelverschraegenbiz@gmail.com



Ghent, Belgium

### **PROFILE**

I have spent the last 4+ years focused on all aspects of software development, ranging from creating applications in React and Vue to building backends in NestJS and PHP.

Besides work, you'll find me in a swimming pool, skiing on the slopes, or quoting "The Office! I love traveling and exploring the hidden gems each city has to offer.

## **SKILLS**

#### SOFT SKILLS

- Communication and coordination
- Leadership
- Problem solver
- Independent
- Curious

#### HARD SKILLS

- JavaScript, TypeScript
- React. Vue
- NestJS, NodeJS
- PHP
- MongoDB, PostgreSQL

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER - AIKIDO**

February 2023 - May 2023

- Help discover product-market-fit with newly built features
- Improve onboarding experience, open-source license scanning, ...

#### **TECH LEAD - CHEQROOM**

July 2022 - February 2023

- Manage and host scrum ceremonies (stand-ups, sprint reviews, ...)
- Communicate and coordinate feature releases and bug fixes
- Unblock team members, provide feedback and technical insights
- Tackle technical debt, large refactors and cleaning up legacy code

## **FULL STACK DEVELOPER - CHEQROOM**

July 2019 - July 2022

- Set up communication layer between our Knockout and React
- Build out design system and accompanying component library
- Set up and deploy GraphQL microservices on AWS
- Automate the deployment process via GitHub Actions

#### Hogeschool Gent (2016 - 2019) **INTERN - RIALTO**

February 2019 - May 2019

- · Learn React, Redux and TypeScript
- Build a floorplan drawing tool based on SVG's

## **EDUCATION**

### APPLIED COMPUTER SCIENCE